woogiworld.com 2011-12-31

# Woogi World - Privacy Policy

---|---|---|---  

We are dedicated to safeguarding any personal information collected online and to helping parents and children learn how to exercise control over personal information while exploring the Internet. We ensure that our privacy policy and our information practices adhere to the U.S. Department of Commerce's Safe Harbor Principles. Because many of the visitors to this site are children, we take care that our content is suitable for children. In addition, we take special measures to help children protect their privacy while online. For example, we do not ask children to disclose more personal information than is necessary for them to participate in a particular activity, and we take efforts to prevent children from posting contact information.

To help ensure a rewarding online experience for our visitors—and for the parents of our visitors who are children—we provide you with this summary of our information practices.

As we continue to offer our visitors new and different types of content and services, we may modify our practices from time to time. However, we will treat all personal information we collect in accordance with the privacy notice in effect at the time the information is collected.

At Woogi World™, the only personally identifiable information we collect from users 12 years old and younger is a parent's valid email address. And we ONLY use this information to send relevant information to the parent or guardian.

For some of our online activities—such as polls or surveys—we may ask users to provide additional information that is not personally identifiable, such as country of residence or a visitor's favorite color.

We always require children under 13 to use a parent or guardians email address instead. 

Additionally, when visitors come to our site, we automatically collect some non-personally identifiable "computer" information, such as the type of computer operating system (e.g., Windows XP or Mac OS), the user's "IP Address", the web browser (e.g., Netscape, Internet Explorer) being used, and information regarding the Internet service provider.

We have created an internal news system that allows us to communicate with the players without sending them information to their personal email address. We do not keep any personal information we obtain beyond the time it is needed. Sometimes we use a visitor's email address to track usage and to ensure users are following the site's Terms and Conditions.

We encourage users to submit their original artwork or other materials via email attachment. We do, however, retain control of how all materials are used and displayed on the Woogi World™ website. Once the artwork or other material is received it is immediately processed and the email is deleted.

We sometimes use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our site, to personalize our visitors' experience on Woogi World™, and to offer products, programs, and services. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze site usage, as well as to offer products, programs, or services.

We will disclose information we maintain when required to do so by law, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena. We also may disclose such information in response to a law enforcement agency's or other public agency's (including schools or children services) request or if we feel that such disclosure may prevent the instigation of a crime.

We will not use or transfer personally identifiable information in ways that are materially different from the ones described above without also providing parental notification of such practices and obtaining consent for any materially different uses.

Woogi World™ is proud of the fact that we do not allow third-party websites to solicit or advertise to our users. Our intention is to keep Woogi World™ free from any sort of direct advertising.

Woogi World™ uses a software technology called "cookies." Cookies are small text files that we place in visitors' computer browsers to store their preferences. Cookies themselves do not contain any personally identifiable information. Although cookies could enable us to relate a visitor's use of this web site to personal information that a visitor has provided, such as an email address, we do not use them for this purpose. We do use cookies to determine how many visitors we have and how often they visit various sections of our site.

We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use the information we collect online.

If you decide to purchase a membership for you or your child, additional information will be required at the time of purchase. That information is not stored by Woogi World™ and is only stored by our financial institution for the purpose of processing payments made to Woogi World™. That information is safeguarded with extremely high, bank-level security and it will never be used for any other purposes.

Parents, please send an email to our Privacy Manager at [support@woogiworld.com](mailto:support@woogiworld.com) if you would like to do any of the following:

Access the personally identifiable information that Woogi World™ has collected online from your child, correct factual errors in such information, request to have this information deleted, or request that we no longer collect or maintain such information.

Please be sure to include your email address and a telephone number where we can reach you. To protect your child's privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to help verify your identity before granting you access to the personal information that we collect and maintain about your child.

Contact us at [support@woogiworld.com](mailto:support@woogiworld.com) should you have any inquiries regarding the privacy policy and/or practices.

The privacy policy set out above is effective as of January 1, 2007, and applies to all information previously obtained by Woogi World™. Woogi World™ reserves the right to change its privacy policy at its sole discretion. Woogi World™ users will be informed of any such change by Woogi World™ posting a new privacy policy on the Woogi World™ website. The effective date of any change of privacy policy will be clearly marked.

If you have any questions, please contact us at [support@woogiworld.com](mailto:support@woogiworld.com).

---
